ride_name = "Slinky Dog Dash"

questions = [
    {
        "question": "What year did Slinky Dog Dash open at Disney's Hollywood Studios?",
        "answers": ["2018", "2017", "2019", "2020"],
        "correct_answer": "2018"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which Disney World park is home to Slinky Dog Dash?",
        "answers": ["Hollywood Studios", "Magic Kingdom", "Epcot", "Animal Kingdom"],
        "correct_answer": "Hollywood Studios"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the theme of Slinky Dog Dash?",
        "answers": ["Toy Story", "Star Wars", "Cars", "Finding Nemo"],
        "correct_answer": "Toy Story"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who designed Slinky Dog Dash?",
        "answers": ["Walt Disney Imagineering", "Tony Baxter", "John Hench", "Bob Gurr"],
        "correct_answer": "Walt Disney Imagineering"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the height requirement to ride Slinky Dog Dash?",
        "answers": ["38 inches", "40 inches", "44 inches", "48 inches"],
        "correct_answer": "38 inches"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the maximum speed of Slinky Dog Dash?",
        "answers": ["40 mph", "35 mph", "45 mph", "50 mph"],
        "correct_answer": "40 mph"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the duration of the Slinky Dog Dash ride?",
        "answers": ["2 minutes", "1 minute 30 seconds", "2 minutes 30 seconds", "3 minutes"],
        "correct_answer": "2 minutes"
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of ride is Slinky Dog Dash?",
        "answers": ["Family roller coaster", "Dark ride", "Simulated ride", "Boat ride"],
        "correct_answer": "Family roller coaster"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the character that the ride vehicle is themed after in Slinky Dog Dash?",
        "answers": ["Slinky Dog", "Buzz Lightyear", "Woody", "Jessie"],
        "correct_answer": "Slinky Dog"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the land where Slinky Dog Dash is located?",
        "answers": ["Toy Story Land", "Star Wars: Galaxy's Edge", "Cars Land", "Pixar Pier"],
        "correct_answer": "Toy Story Land"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the toy that Slinky Dog Dash is based on?",
        "answers": ["Slinky", "Buzz Lightyear", "Woody", "Jessie"],
        "correct_answer": "Slinky"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the song played during the ride in Slinky Dog Dash?",
        "answers": ["You've Got a Friend in Me", "We Belong Together", "Strange Things", "I Will Go Sailing No More"],
        "correct_answer": "You've Got a Friend in Me"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the character who gives the safety instructions in Slinky Dog Dash?",
        "answers": ["Woody", "Buzz Lightyear", "Jessie", "Rex"],
        "correct_answer": "Woody"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the character who appears at the end of the ride in Slinky Dog Dash?",
        "answers": ["Wheezy", "Buzz Lightyear", "Woody", "Jessie"],
        "correct_answer": "Wheezy"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the toy company that makes Slinky Dog?",
        "answers": ["James Industries", "Mattel", "Hasbro", "Fisher-Price"],
        "correct_answer": "James Industries"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the character who is a cowboy in Toy Story?",
        "answers": ["Woody", "Buzz Lightyear", "Jessie", "Bullseye"],
        "correct_answer": "Woody"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the character who is a space ranger in Toy Story?",
        "answers": ["Buzz Lightyear", "Woody", "Jessie", "Rex"],
        "correct_answer": "Buzz Lightyear"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the character who is a cowgirl in Toy Story?",
        "answers": ["Jessie", "Woody", "Buzz Lightyear", "Bullseye"],
        "correct_answer": "Jessie"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the character who is a dinosaur in Toy Story?",
        "answers": ["Rex", "Woody", "Buzz Lightyear", "Jessie"],
        "correct_answer": "Rex"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the character who is a piggy bank in Toy Story?",
        "answers": ["Hamm", "Woody", "Buzz Lightyear", "Jessie"],
        "correct_answer": "Hamm"
    }
]